export const econ2301Data = {
    "cengage":{
        "module1":[
            {
              "Question": "Which of the following best describes the reason why the division of labor allows individuals and firms to specialize and produce more?",
              "Answer": "It allows individuals and firms to take advantage of economies of scale."
            },
            {
              "Question": "In the ______________, households receive goods and services and pay firms for them.",
              "Answer": "goods and services market"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Fill in the blank with the correct answer by typing in the box. Microeconomics focuses on the actions of individual agents within the economy, and macroeconomics looks at the economy as a _________.",
              "Answer": "whole"
            },
            {
              "Question": "In the ____________, households work and receive payment from firms.",
              "Answer": "labor market"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Economies that are primarily market oriented have fewer regulations.",
              "Answer": "TRUE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Economics is the study of how humans make decisions in the face of scarcity.",
              "Answer": "TRUE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "A theory is a simplified representation of how two or more variables interact with each other.",
              "Answer": "TRUE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Fill in the blank with the correct answer by typing in the box. The circular flow diagram shows how households and firms interact in the goods and services market, and in the _______ market.",
              "Answer": "labor"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Macroeconomics and microeconomics are concerned with the well-being of only people with jobs and high incomes, they just examine it from a different perspective.",
              "Answer": "FALSE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "In what geographic areas would a market-oriented system that remains closer to the command economy end of the spectrum most likely be found?",
              "Answer": "China and Russia"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which of the following best describes the difference(s) between a model and a theory?",
              "Answer": "A theory is a more abstract representation, while a model is more applied or empirical representation."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which of the following is most likely an example of specialization?",
              "Answer": "Only those with medical degrees qualify to become doctors."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Fill in the blank with the correct answer by typing in the box. Most economies in the real world are _________; they combine elements of command and market systems.",
              "Answer": "mixed"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Fill in the blank with the correct answer by typing in the box. Scarcity means that human wants for goods, services, and resources ______________ what is available.",
              "Answer": "exceed"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Macroeconomics primarily examines",
              "Answer": "broad issues such as national output, employment, and inflation."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which of the following statements most likely lies within the realm of microeconomics?",
              "Answer": "An increase in labor costs will increase the additional cost of producing another bus."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Matching: Market",
              "Answer": "Economies based on supply and demand"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Matching: Traditional",
              "Answer": "Economies that organize their economic affairs the way they have always done"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Matching: Command",
              "Answer": "Economies that are devoted to goals passed down from a ruler or ruling class"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Globalization has most likely occurred for which of the following reasons?",
              "Answer": "International agreements and treaties between countries have encouraged greater trade."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Macroeconomics",
              "Answer": "is concerned with the expansion and contraction of the overall economy."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which of the following is most likely an example of the division of labor?",
              "Answer": "A restaurant divides up the task of serving meals into a range of jobs like top chef, sous chefs, less-skilled kitchen help, and servers to wait on the tables."
            }
          ],
        "module2":[
            {
              "Question": "The production possibility frontier has a straight shape because of the law of diminishing returns.",
              "Answer": "FALSE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "The economy below can produce either jets or guns.  If the economy produces 1 jet then it can produce 100 guns, however if the economy increases production of jets to 2 then production of guns decreases to 90, and so on.  What is the opportunity cost of producing the 3rd jet.",
              "Answer": "20 guns"
            },
            {
              "Question": "The lesson of __________ is to forget about the money that’s irretrievably gone and instead to focus on the marginal costs and benefits of future options.",
              "Answer": "sunk costs"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which of the following statements best describes trade-offs?",
              "Answer": "With a trade-off, it is necessary to give up some of one good to gain more of the other good."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which of the following is a normative statement?",
              "Answer": "The minimum wage should be raised."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Refer to the graph. An economy is operating at full employment, and then the economy experiences a recession. This change is portrayed in the movement from",
              "Answer": "C to G."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Matching: Marginal Analysis",
              "Answer": "Comparison of the benefits and costs of a choice"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Matching: Law of diminishing marginal utility",
              "Answer": "The level of benefit decreases as consumption increases"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Matching: Utility",
              "Answer": "Satisfaction obtained from a good or service"
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which of the following statement(s) best describes scarcity?",
              "Answer": "Even if the budget constraint or a PPF shifts, scarcity remains—just at a different level."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Refer to the graph. Along the production possibilities frontier, the most efficient point of production depicted is",
              "Answer": "All points on the production possibilities frontier are equally efficient."
            },
            {
              "Question": "Which of the following statements best describes productive efficiency?",
              "Answer": "Productive efficiency occurs when it is impossible to produce more of one good (or service) without decreasing the quantity produced of another good (or service)."
            },
            {
              "Question": "In many cases, it is reasonable to refer to the opportunity cost as the price.",
              "Answer": "TRUE"
            },
            {
              "Question": "The law of ____________________________ explains why people and societies get less utility from the additional consumption of a good or service.",
              "Answer": "diminishing marginal utility"
            }
          ],
        "module3":[
            {
                "Question": "Peanuts are used to make peanut butter. Suppose that the price of peanuts increase. What would you expect to happen to the equilibrium price and quantity of peanut butter due to the increase in the price of peanuts?",
                "Answer": "price of peanut butter would increase and quantity of peanut butter sold would decrease"
              },
              {
                "Question": "Which of the following statements best describes the relationship between price and quantity demanded for a given good or service?",
                "Answer": "A rise in price of a good or service almost always decreases the quantity demanded of that good or service."
              },
              {
                "Question": "When an economic event causes demand or supply to shift, prices and quantities will move in the general direction of equilibrium.",
                "Answer": "TRUE"
              },
              {
                "Question": "Refer to the graph. A change from Point A to Point B represents a(n)",
                "Answer": "increase in quantity supplied."
              },
              {
                "Question": "Which statement most accurately describes what happens when both supply and demand curves shift?",
                "Answer": "When both curves shift, typically we can determine the overall effect on price or on quantity, but not on both."
              },
              {
                "Question": "Which statement is most likely correct about quantity supplied?",
                "Answer": "When economists refer to quantity supplied, they are referring to a certain point on the supply curve or a certain quantity on the supply schedule."
              },
              {
                "Question": "The point where the supply curve and the demand curve cross is called the equilibrium.",
                "Answer": "TRUE"
              },
              {
                "Question": "Interpret the following statement: \"An increase in the price of wheat will encourage farmers to increase the quantity of wheat supplied to the market.",
                "Answer": "The statement is correct."
              },
              {
                "Question": "________________ —a term describing a tool that economists use to determine the effect of an economic event on equilibrium price and quantity.",
                "Answer": "The four-step process"
              },
              {
                "Question": "The price where quantity demanded is equal to quantity supplied is known as",
                "Answer": "equilibrium price."
              },
              {
                "Question": "The Honda Civic is considered a more fuel efficient vehicle. Suppose that gas prices increase. What would you expect to happen in the market for Honda Civics?",
                "Answer": "the demand curve shifts to the right."
              },
              {
                "Question": "Select whether the statement is true or false.",
                "Answer": "TRUE"
              },
              {
                "Question": "_________________ refers to the total number of units that are purchased at that price.",
                "Answer": "Quantity demanded"
              },
              {
                "Question": "Which statement(s) are most likely correct about supply?",
                "Answer": "A rise in price almost always leads to an increase in the quantity supplied of that good."
              },
              {
                "Question": "Which of the following statements best describes excess demand, or shortage?",
                "Answer": "The area between the supply and demand curves below the equilibrium point is called excess demand, or shortage."
              },
              {
                "Question": "A severe freeze has once again damaged the Florida orange crop. The impact on the market for orange juice will be a leftward shift of",
                "Answer": "the supply curve."
              },
              {
                "Question": "Economists use the term supply to refer to the amount of some good or service a customer is willing to supply at each price.",
                "Answer": "FALSE"
              },
              {
                "Question": "Refer to the graph. A change from Supply Curve S2 to S1 is called a(n)",
                "Answer": "increase in supply."
              },
              {
                "Question": "Which of the following statements best describes excess supply, or surplus?",
                "Answer": "The area between the supply and demand curves above the equilibrium point is called excess supply, or surplus."
              },
              {
                "Question": "Economists use the term demand to refer to the amount of some good or service consumers are willing and able to purchase at each price.",
                "Answer": "TRUE"
              },
              {
                "Question": "In economics, the demand for a good refers to the amount of the good that people",
                "Answer": "will buy at various prices."
              }
            
            ]
    }
}
